I'll talk about the regular meeting of toxic cancer board on the day of June 2, 2021.
There are a lot of students who have other hearing on the codes just for years.
We only only want to be able to do this budget.
We have a team one that I'd like to ask you about.
Quite good.
So we're going to lead into the three of the people that have a personal character.
We have a group of four executive gender.
So that's what we're going to do.
We're going to do about five to four-team.
We've got the five.
That will be fun.
15 was the first class of our parents or teachers' vision.
That they would be a good person.
Good evening, we're on the case of our students.
The C.O. and the C.O.
We're also also a part of our academy.
I'm here to see a couple of reasons that our students are going to be.
I'll take you on some of the real cool things that are happening in our community.
And then we're tuned to ask for your partnership on our strategic vision.
We've been for as a club.
I'm sorry to go over a couple of days on the high-end first.
The first one is our vision.
That was the first club.
Then you asked me, I was here to know what we do with the first class.
Some of you may know it.
So we have a couple of new council members.
The big extension of the first class is to enable all the other people to reach our full potential.
Whatever that people would like for them.
We do that through focus on three priority areas.
I can introduce a specific area that is said in the chat that we don't see by some of us.
In our office, we will, as to keep it as a graduate at my school,
we'll apply it in our future.
We send under the future, because that might be different for everyone in our community.
It's not always college.
It's not always career.
And then it came in between.
The one thing I do want to point out about is as close to ourselves as a lot of the academy.
We are the largest provider that we've developed for our community.
We're also the only year-round youth development organization in the academy.
We are the ones providing consistent and quality programs too.
is new, and any of the dreams of the future.
A little bit about the types of families that we start, the DSI observed.
The 15% of our families, as I showed up here,
let's have a little bit of federal poverty.
45% of our members are a member of American.
We are actually registered, a member of the local police enforcement of the American.
As a large organization, they have services,
services, or the largest provider of services in the Indian country.
80% of our members are 12 years old, and we'll have a little bit of a lot of it.
So, clear how we've been as a organization.
We've been around in 1990.
We've been able to play an important role in the creation of our organization.
We have a shape on it.
As we continue to report, we have a couple of things to understand.
Our first building was in a time when we were building,
we were building next to a time to jump, and maybe as familiar with that one.
We have three organizations, five members of their own.
We also have a four-ish location.
And from 2000 to 2017, our average living attendance was around 57 kids.
Our 2016 budget was also around $6,000,000.
I want you to turn it over to those last two that average living attendance
and the budget, as we've made to look forward to that one,
but we have hundreds.
So, wherever we have right now, while we're in our new home,
and which is the former National Guard Guard Building,
we've been in the June of 2017.
We have two physical buildings and one school site,
so we're just building a public environment, and we have a social site and a fairerment.
Today, our average living attendance is around $6,000,000,
but we're excited to get a day.
But our registered membership,
which means any kid has participated in any of our programs throughout the year,
heard the names at 600 and 35 days.
And in the summer, by right now, today's the first day of our summer program,
we all survived to be a total lifetime.
Until our summer members are much higher as you see.
Our 2019 budget, around $2,000,000, and then the day that we have it,
and we are going to secure the first part of the CARES Act
that our daughters have been in part of the Human Services,
which she and the Canadian Research Project in 2020.
In 2020, one who has estimated to be around $5,000,
$2,000 a year, maybe we can do a partnership with a homeless safe part of the education.
We just wish somebody an intern into a partnership,
using high-sortons, which we'll talk about here in a little bit.
Our current building is about $10,000,
which is about $10,000 for our foot,
as four classrooms, a gymnasium,
and we can act on that,
so around $5,000 to $2,705.
And...
Our current state, we partnered with the Port of the Community Organization, like my
fellow driver, that the NTAJS, for things like couldn't be called drug needs.
The partner of the agency on the conservation management, and what I think is one of the
most important part of the relationship is with my fellow schools, whether some of our academic
support.
We all know that there's some of our young side things for which we're going to be a dynamic,
but it's even more prevalent in families holding that umbrella of our family.
So this summer we had teachers coming in and reiterating to work with kids on the basic
community I'm having, reading skills, and making sure they're not following me in further
talking about it in school.
A little bit on our COVID-19 response, I'm having the chance to emphasize what kind of
things that are happening.
We are a full force in the head and agricultural program, and it started spreading our
program with our diverse life diversity down in March 2020.
That was wrong for us, but what wasn't wrong for us on the site was that we had to continue
to be something.
We couldn't just close our doors and say it would be back when we somebody means let's say it.
So what we did was transition to more of a food delivery program, provides support to families
basic needs.
So we started to grab an ambulance over 35,000 meals, to families that were just following
the miraculous event, that was a food process, and we got this out of the door to our families.
Thankfully, we were going to re-entend our doors in June 2020, which if you were going to
almost really high COVID in our area, we were going to open at the second day of our
day-mine site, so 200 and 20 kids.
One of the things I like to point out in June 2020, when I was like a COVID in our community, we
had only two cases of COVID in our entire summer program.
We were going to, I saw, like, those two cases, and we had no convenience for our organization.
So we were going to take a certain case and show others in the community, but maybe they could
be sent into the area as well, so like we began to re-open our community resources.
In August 2020, the opportunity came with the activation appointed Department of Human Services.
So open our community's first single community, Opsen, something to be very proud of, they're
only 16 community of Opseners in the state, we were chosen to be one of them, and one of those
health centers for the time being to use open our doors for 10 hours a day, for kids who are
out of school, but still had tons of virtual school work to get done.
Many of the families did not enter that home, they didn't have people to supervise their children,
they didn't have food, and they weren't, they weren't in the home.
So we open the Help Center, and we open the entire race,
since August 2020.
We're providing the Help Support through
and just to know support in our social and emotional needs.
All of this is a say, where are you going?
And where's the why and where's your time?
It's to talk to you about where we're headed
and where we're going to your partnership,
to see the environment, but also as our council members and the ears.
So let's see over here.
We're going to see with the last four years,
our numbers and enrollment.
These are registered numbers.
And then reminding you these are kids attending
our program at any time throughout the year.
And so in 2020,
how we see this, can our numbers work
many to identify COVID.
But what I want to point out is,
our orders group was in the 11 to 18-year-old kids.
Those middle school and high school pictures.
And in those 11 to 18-year-olds in law,
our orders, they should see a hundred and thirty-one percent increase.
What makes a hundred and thirty-one percent increase,
is that we have one teamer at our right website.
So we have our current space that we're in.
It's very easy to think,
we've done about the four-year-old,
we've got to find the building.
But what we have to do is to continue to support kids.
We can't stop here.
The need is very hard to believe.
And we must start with our ways to start with our kids.
We're strategic to community partnerships.
And we hope we can start on any schedule or current one.
So with the need and our community,
I would like to talk to you about.
It's all right.
What's happening with our kids.
Part of the community around the country.
The most important one is that we have loads of knocker
on the basis between our three and seven of the year.
That's in the critical moment of your initial hours.
When they researchers,
they're about approximately forty-one, two hours.
Then they're between twenty and twenty-one, so far.
But also three out of ten kids will charge theirhyuk once a year.
They are community internationally.
We have a real area of growth around age,
graduating in high school,
and it may be going back to that to the point in the future.
We don't have to start charging food at my six age.
and see a Instagram group of people.
Currently, there are 10,000 and 7,300,000 kids
waiting on their social spots, so only because we
don't know the facilities, the staff and the money to do so.
And when we look at our current graduation rate,
it's low in the state average, and there are
unpaid visits for services for children to be martyred.
And here's great to do something, and we must.
So where?
That's right.
it's exciting stuff that I get to tell you about.
So if you're searching for partition
with my own public schools, we are going to enter the team here
and we'll need you to use all of our other schools
as our secondary site.
We're just going to start by producing the North
into the other line of the North school,
has nothing to do with the experiment
that is the most of the problem with the North school.
So we're going to see the North side, which has been
with the English, coffee, alcohol, and all the way down
is the cafeteria.
So we can use some of our 12 classrooms,
a general of the cafeteria and more in four states.
Today, we will say this morning,
we had about 100 and 50 break-ins today.
One of the cool things is that we're doing a part of the North
of the North Healing House to put it on site, just.
So that kids who need support,
what they're going to help us pass on on site,
that they can use.
We're also partnering with the Marine Academy
to provide leadership partners in the North Florida School.
We'll be sharing this space with the Academy
and the North Florida School, so that they can use
some of our cool, game-tune equipment,
or some of our current world leadership programs.
Things like that, we have resources to provide,
and they have to kids and share the space.
The biggest thing is to provide
back to our services.
We all know there's a lot of productive things
that we start using these teenagers to know
where our kids are going to learn.
We must begin to identify
productive things for our kids to do.
We want to start a Friday and Saturday night job
and service, meaning that kids can come
by dollar or in Friday night,
ending up with our friends in quite cool
and watching movies and needs snacks,
and a safe and supervised fashion.
We also, the biggest part of our dream
for this space and our children,
is to remember our job's last training,
internship, place in the college you're ready and matured.
We want to look this on permission,
so that we can get qualified for courses in this area,
and we know that's a complicated way to answer it.
But with the partnership, we can put them
on the front side where kids are distilled
so they call it their jobs to be the mistake,
and we have to think they've worked on things like
soft sales in the leadership of our friends for our little guys.
So that when I think that I spent a call
by the minute job, I think it's an opportunity.
So of course, I think this partnership,
as we begin with a new superintendant,
I have a lot of faith in this partnership
with a send pass that you hear at the moment of your work.
And so I hope that we can continue using it for future years,
but if not, in this space, it has to be an emergency space.
And that's why I want to talk to you guys
about how we're going to do it.
How are we going to make this team center happen?
How are we going to make this sustainable for our community?
And how are we going to start the building into the hospital here?
My attention is that you have third part of your eight-point city.
The time of your time of partners are school partners using the American University plan.
And the ones that maybe, you know, of course, are coming to our cities, are coming to our schools, and everything in which we need.
I just want to add that I'm not coming to you, I'm not coming to you, I'm not coming to you.
I'm coming to you asking for attention to conversations on how we can work together using the using an American University plan.
And in partnership with all of the other things I have us in there.
The one here that I do know is, in those of us, both of us under, is number two of the American University plan.
That's certainly the hardest thing to do in any of these activities.
You know, let's see how we're going to use some of this one.
We've talked about our very educational services like two of our international partners.
We're going to go to each other's environment, simply in the U.S. and the high quality child care.
And so I think this evening is an important thing to do with that.
What that really is done is been a long way.
So I do just want to touch on that.
I believe we have a real opportunity to work together through the American University plan.
And this is our city government to begin talking about a five-way way.
Some partner just sort of more things that aren't community.
The need is right.
And we must all work together, which I think we're doing very good community.
We're all of those people are one of the partners of the club.
And I think that it opens our part here with us to continue these conversations.
If you have any questions, what do you want to do?
I mentioned a team center, if that's separate.
It's going to be decided to be a team center.
No, that is our team center.
So this summer we're going to realize that as additional support,
but it's just a third-party kids.
When it transition out of summer, we're going to be tactical program.
There will be a traditional team center.
So if a kid is anywhere from the books and the books and the books and the most school in the high school,
we'll all attend after school program at our new team center at the most school.
Then our room is decided to only start a kid's up third-party.
So maybe a kid's first-off thinking,
we're coming to the prison tonight.
The kid's got his amazing job.
I got to go out of the two.
A few months ago, if you've ever been in a chance to go to a facility
and watch you be able to do in such a small space.
He's extremely impressive.
She's very innovative.
She has a great idea of this great staff.
Very little of the execute.
He'll be in the space with him.
to create, obviously, it's mainly the needs of the kids,
because the kids are showing up, the knowledge and the need.
I think she's providing a service that's
much needed, it doesn't make some job.
She's obviously very distant, which also offers her knowledge,
because she's being managed to really stretch
with London, and provide her really great opportunity
for these kids to come socialize in that safe environment
of her to great sites.
It's somewhere higher than she and the way to walk up.
She goes to the kids and all the children.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Good to you, you use this mentors and stuff
with those teens, type settings in the evening.
So we have all the things that we have
that are in the public professionals,
that we use is our primary mentors.
These are going to be a traditional college students
or college graduates that we employ at the club.
We also use some of our community partners
to provide mentors as well, and get kids
and adults back into our club.
They're going to be really on the level
to have many volunteers, because of the safety precautions.
So we're going to take a couple of their tours
and see volunteers and people who want to mentor,
or strong partners who provide the tips here in my own.
I serve on their board of directors.
And we want to form those relationships
so that we can bring experts in our club
that can provide necessary services.
We're going to be going to be the end of tomorrow.
We want to further advance to our community
to provide opportunities to our kids.
That they might not ever get elsewhere.
It is how it goes to most of them.
Our kids will need those services.
Hey, here.
Thank you.
Over 16, this is the year 20,
21, 22, and this is a budget message.
The resolution you're going to see on,
put one of the questions that you're going to come up with,
that's the reason why you're going to see.
The only comment I have to make,
then I'll answer any questions,
is on the resolution that was a scripted error.
It's just a fiscal year.
It needs to say a second.
It's a second, whereas it should say, June 30, 2022,
or fiscal year 21, 2021, 2021, 2021.
The effort that you'll find open the questions
that you can go into the weeds if you want
to prepare the answer to the question.
Mr. Mayor, you're just as reminded to view
from the rest of the council.
This is the budget that we have a couple of opportunities
on the past months that we met in the beginning
in a through the budget, in a relationship with questions,
and that you'll have that time as well as the rest of the time.
We've also talked to you in the committee
to do it in the future.
So that we can kind of get a name of tax derivative and very almost a trade-in's post-pandemic.
So again, this budget is in my message of missions that we were very conservative in use
of the expectation of the tax derivative for next year.
So in the nearer view, probably would be wise.
And it also just reminded the council that obviously the council has even before you
afforded it to a name of the budget, and then just in the nearer view.
And this is not your national opportunity.
I'll be seeing this budget in probably a moment.
You also will see the majority of the media that have setfully in the march,
in the acquisitions that are done.
We'll come and put the council in the nearer view.
I've left the discussions favorable about our budget.
We're going to go on and see the United States.
We'd like to see and learn more about all of the different funding mechanisms for our budget.
And have those on the spur.
I think it will make us watch the council and make us more aware and better allocate this money to gain understanding
of those things that is opportunity to set up.
Of all part of the Twitter and the media and how to prepare for those money is done.
So I guess I'm asking if any time I'll talk to you,
to present themselves to be involved on every question.
I'm going to create these opportunities to come in.
I'll be fine.
So, you mentioned being taken out of the common question.
It was very limited.
Like, what is that?
What is considered to be taken?
Is there a dollar figure that if we go all over this amount,
that's what it's going to be.
So, once you approve the budget, that's the budget.
The city manager has the ability to move money.
So, we have 200 funds.
One of the funds is the city fund, the general fund.
We have the initiative, eight fund, which is the utility fund.
We have the health insurance fund.
There's 29 of those kind of funds.
The city manager has the ability to move money inside each fund.
You can't move money across funds.
And if we can't afford it, a grant.
A budget, a minimum, will come to you to amend the budget to say,
eight or any of this money, and we're going to spend it.
So, we're going to get this revenue, and then we're going to spend this revenue.
So, any time, any of those members change,
except for within, the bottom line number,
and time, the bottom line number changes.
That's as much of them within the council.
if they could get the dollar, I mean, and can't, and can't, but change it in any way.
And then specifically, any active positions that are done,
at the shoulder, under cling list,
the camps could improve to the camps.
Sure, a lot of requests being used to participate working
through 27 dollars, but it was already budgeted this table.
Is there a differential, and a little bit of that?
number that we, it's budgeted, you can even rely on it, looking through the list, there's
9,000 dollars for free.
That's not going to be something that we're going to go to.
And that's kind of what I was wondering.
What's that?
And then it's very active to kind of be the answer to the work of the group.
We're going to work even though it's been different than the budget.
Priorization.
I think it's your question.
All right.
So, Eric, it's been a share with all the clients that you're playing as a list.
You have proof.
Everything.
We can pay for utility.
By six, that you can pay for.
Like utility bills that come in.
That we know we're going to pay for that.
By six, that you can pay before you pay before you approve the client.
But otherwise, you have proof before we perfect the purchase.
I was going to say I didn't do a couple of things.
So, you think you could have committed it.
We're going to take it for the council.
So, we have to be that way.
I think it will be that way.
So, we take it for the council.
Yeah, I think that will be that.
Thank you.
Can you pay for the proof?
Yes.
Proof.
Can you give questions on that?
We'll just keep on there, we'll see you guys.
So when
Great team in the business
My team in satin works for the 20 man and counting community in others to further reinforce our larger partner
the partner, that the peaceful version is trying to be in mind, and they close today on the
mode to have a crush on the turn by me. I don't know what that's going to lead to, but it's
going to clean up, it creates a lot of energy. So there's no way to get the two projects down,
and they've got started for us to blow them up. So that's a significant investment in
not cleaning, they've proven to be a good partner on other projects, and we actually had
lots with drag speeders that the hammer was able to piece a little bit, right? Sorry, right before
you go to some papers. But I don't know if drag speed is all for our day man, but he is definitely
really the best part of the year. We're going to go to this door between the few people who
are joining their stronghold and right now they've all the 21st or the 14th of the 17th.
Our stage is all of us. We're not sure where they are, I think it's the 21st at 10 a.m. they're going to do the
groundwork, and certainly in there, but they've been excited to talk to us last time. So we're going to take a
journey down, and he's got some ideas of what to do with that property, but whatever it is,
it's going to be good for our community. And then that much on a Friday, if you've been into it,
if that's about sponsorship, you're going to succeed in success. Let's have a look. So he's
moving to a really good partner that life's been his money, and we see his own people appreciate.
So he's got a ground sheet. He asked me about the festival. I'll call him about it and he said this.
and he's not sponsored on here, right?
So, but he's a great partner for the story of working out.
Yeah, they go into the festival that we made the last week,
the official National Service, the fall festival,
all of the 266 festival, the main first staff,
have been filled with the come call, come call, come call.
This is going to be bigger than, but I think they're great.
We first started through a lot of people,
this community could go that weekend.
Brian, as the little ones, the little ones,
the second one, the second one, the festival.
Going to keep our advances.
You can send out 100 members of the west of the park.
And that's just a bit of a set up for food trucks.
And the interviews, the works were pretty, pretty wild.
Across the whole park.
So we're having this cycle of another community that said,
they're watching us.
Because they want to be one.
And they want to see how we do it.
And so it's a very community.
So I don't know if you kind of feel good,
if you're actually watching us,
and see how we cool this off.
And then my last question is, how am I going to be there?
You know, Eric's artwork, and this help us, help the nestled.
And so now it's like we're going to be a part of it,
to someone else, to help them to do the same kind of later.
But I think we're not going to have to have,
so people go around with it, to be able to communicate
or communicate with them.
Because we've got to make sure the details to this,
and don't be huge.
We're going to have the rest of us going to have an interview.
We have to have the stage of the event.
We have to have the rest of the stage of the event.
We've just before we go there,
there are many of them that we're having,
like, a semi-low beer, a wink,
and another variety of things.
So there are possible details that are going into this.
That's just for me.
But there's actually a lot going to go through this,
but I agree with you.
It's very, very nicely what else we had.
There's always something to go along with.
But I'm excited about it.
I know our action from the National Bank.
And it's going to be a conversation about the time of the beer.
Then you come home, help us with the personal.
It makes it easier to work with folks when there's,
give you a special discussion.
We're going to go for a mess of it.
That's not going to be able to understand it.
So what else?
I don't know what else.
But I have both the time of that.
So it's in the year four and a seven weeks away.
And it's probably not here for that,
but I'd be there a bit of a week later.
the chief program that is our most scary,
which is step by step, I'm saying to you now.
So, this makes eye to go forward
to all the press that the management
put that from that TV, the radio, the right area.
This is going to be a big matter for the media, so look forward to it.
I think I ran the clock today.
That's how you name it.
So, that's the thing to be true about the management issue.
All right.
A lot of that's an additional side of the news to the lay on the right.
So, today, we're going to provide a week and a word
775,000 dollar fee in my acquisition rate.
It's a great amount of the acquisition,
a village of nine residential structures,
a great commercial structure.
That also have not been identified, yes, because it's a great deal.
Obviously, it's nothing to see that 775,000,
but that is a cost for required properties from commercial properties.
It is a 775, 25, and actually a city,
the city will automatically find a really neat and code.
So, that'll be from cat and sewer inspections,
and this makes it a piece of things like that,
and also it's a piece of cost.
But the huge issue is, again,
if you do a commercial properties as well,
if you can make sure what those are actually,
if they haven't been negotiated yet,
and if those didn't work properly, we'll start talking.
See if we've been negotiating that for those properties,
we've been looking forward to seeing that.
Again, these properties are probably still a red tag,
they're in the main point of the team.
What?
So, these are properties that you can go with.
This first meeting is actually going to be this week,
all of the part of the members came into the moment.
It's very, very good to look.
That we would say to the public,
and we'll give you a details.
So, I hope you'll provide an information on that.
Can I speak?
Additionally, the fire and the housing authority
has been awarded the $1,000,000 housing authority.
That great recovery of renovation,
both the nine drives tower and nine towers.
We're at the east side of the couple.
First meeting for that project is a display
between June 27th and April details of that.
We will look excited to provide that feedback to us.
Two of you's opportunity is from on the certainty
of those all of whom I can give it to you.
Additionally, I want to make note that our...
2020 first meeting council meeting, we're going to be looking at possibly moving on date,
Title Cline, and I actually be on the 10th, the 10th and the very power of our association
conference with the other municipalities of our region, and for that, we have the staff
to have the unique decision, and then how much should we want to be in second, especially
to be able to play a Sunday morning meeting, just want to put that in the work of the
I actually got that.
What is it?
I don't know if I'm going to use it all the way.
You guys need to do it every day, right?
We can go back to Europe one in a time.
Right there.
So, he says, T-set, possibly, it's in the grant.
He got me also in the T-set, up into the grant, awarded this district.
And so, it's here to send a facial or a life take.
It's talking about, you know, it's a T-set grant, awarded in your life, it's like a district.
T-set, awarded the T-set, up into the grant, to the city of Miami.
The city of Miami, those were 24,000 dollars a year.
But the route C-C-C-C-C-C-Ox splash pad side, this grant was provided to ensure that
local children have increased.
Increase opportunities in these places, by it.
So, I don't know if that's enough before, but...
T-set.
I don't know if there's an answer.
But eight seconds ago, people were in the last group.
It's the sort of self-renewable, yes.
So on that 20 first, Doug, we actually need to go for the inter-pointing A.
If you go on the Monday, it's 14 p.m. on the day.
It's really the four over the 20 A.s each actor.
We might have to have a lot of them here on the foot.
Okay.
That's up to you.
You may want to have without me.
You're like, I don't know that.
Do you have any questions over your arm?
I'm going to leave you alone.
Joe, this artist paying bills as a matter, thank you for being able to have it.
We do have council work session, please.
Thank you.
Let's get going for you.
Let's work with us.
We need to have it.
All right.
Thank you.
So if you could join us in the role,
Is it all the money?
All the money?
All right.
Okay.
We're going to do a check.
I'm going to do a check.
So look.
Turn back.
Okay.
And also five.
Five.